Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
- UBWA (International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink, and Distillery Workers of America), Publication (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Hourly earnings in brewing and manufacturing industries, 1956-1958 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Use movies at meetings, Publication (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: What do you saylet's get our beer and liquor back to a price we can afford to pay, Publication (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Where your dues money goes, 1959; Publication (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Non-productive pay allowances in brewery contracts, 1959; Publication (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Paid Holidays including benefits negotiated through 1960 December 1958, Publication (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Union dues -- your best investment, Publication (Box 114, Folder 7)
- UBWA (International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink, and Distillery Workers of America), Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Jubilee Festival and Twenty-fifth Anniversary, Brewers' Union, number one, 1909; Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Propositions for the consideration of the Delegates to the Seventeenth Convention of the International Union of the United Brewery Workmen of America, Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Protokoll uber die verhandlungen der vierten jahres, 1889; Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Report of the Int. Secretaries and the Editor in both English and German, 1902; Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Report of the Int. Secretaries and the Editor in both English and German, 1903; Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Report of the Int. Secretaries and the Editor in both English and German, 1908; Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Report of the International Officers to the Delegates of the Nineteenth Convention, 1912; Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: United Brewery Workers, Annual, 1906; Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Banquet Concert and Ball, 25th Anniversary Celebration, 1911; Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
- UBWA (International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink, and Distillery Workers of America), Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Age, Purity, Strength, 1906; Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
    Notes: Very brittle
- UBWA (International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink, and Distillery Workers of America), Publication (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Au die delegaten der 13. konvention, Publication (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Protokoll der special-convention der ver. Brauerei-arbeiter der ber. Staaten, 1888; Publication (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: To the delegates of the special convention to be held April 2nd, 1899, Publication (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: To the delegates assembled in special convention, Publication (Box 114, Folder 10)
- UBWA (International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink, and Distillery Workers of America), Publication (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New York City meeting 75 years ago led to present day union, 1961; Publication (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Union with a heart, 1961; Publication (Box 115, Folder 1)
    Author: Maurer, Fleisher & Associates, inc., Washington, D.C.
    Notes: Copy 3
- UBWA (International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink, and Distillery Workers of America), Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers, A.F.L.-C.I.O. - Contract Statistical Information, 1961; Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers, A.F.L.-C.I.O. - Contract Statistical Information, 1962; Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers, A.F.L.-C.I.O. - Contract Statistical Information, 1963; Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers, A.F.L.-C.I.O. - Contract Statistical Information, 1967; Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Copy of a 'Welcome' letter from the Int'l. Union of United Brewery", Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
- UBWA (International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink, and Distillery Workers of America), Publication (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Labors stake in the licensed beverage industry, 1962; Publication (Box 115, Folder 3)
- UBWA (International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink, and Distillery Workers of America), Publication (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers, A.F.L.-C.I.O. - Contract Statistical Information, 1964; Publication (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers, A.F.L.-C.I.O. - Contract Statistical Information, 1965; Publication (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers, A.F.L.-C.I.O. - Contract Statistical Information, 1966; Publication (Box 115, Folder 4)
- UBWA (International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink, and Distillery Workers of America), Publication (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers, A.F.L.-C.I.O. - Contract Statistical Information, 1967; Publication (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers, A.F.L.-C.I.O. - Contract Statistical Information, 1968; Publication (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers, A.F.L.-C.I.O. - Contract Statistical Information, 1969; Publication (Box 115, Folder 5)
- UBWA (International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink, and Distillery Workers of America), Publication (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers, A.F.L.-C.I.O. - Contract Statistical Information, 1970; Publication (Box 115, Folder 6)
- UBWA (International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink, and Distillery Workers of America), Publication (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Get on the team: some answers, Publication (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Study guide for use with 'Know your Union', (Shop Steward's Manual), Publication (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: The Story of the Brewery Workers, 1952; Publication (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Use movies at meetings, Publication (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Your strike assistance program, Publication (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Correspondence - from Int'l. Union of United Brewery, Flour to International Vice Presidents, Regional Directors, International Rep, 1961; Publication (Box 115, Folder 7)
    Notes: Regarding second annual campaign for subscriptions to Consumer Reports.
  - Item 7: Know your union, Publication (Box 115, Folder 7)
- United States. Bureau of Apprenticeship and Training, Publication (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Brief history of the United Brick & Clay Workers of America, Publication (Box 116, Folder 1)
- United States. Bureau of Apprenticeship and Training, Publication (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Seventeen suggestions to company and union representatives who plan to participate in arbitration proceedings, Publication (Box 116, Folder 2)
- United States. Bureau of Apprenticeship and Training, Publication (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Historical Boston, for the Delegates attending the Forty-Second Convention of the Bricklayers and Masons, 1908; Publication (Box 116, Folder 3)
    Notes: Souvenir program
- United States. Bureau of Apprenticeship and Training, Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: National bricklaying apprenticeship program and standards prepared and approved by the National Joint Bricklaying Apprenticeship Committee..., 1961; Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
    Author: United States. Bureau of Apprenticeship and Training.
  - Item 2: Approved standards of apprenticeship training for marble setting, Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
- United States. Bureau of Apprenticeship and Training, Publication (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Labor personality of the month, Harry C. Bates, 1942; Publication (Box 116, Folder 5)
- United States. Bureau of Apprenticeship and Training, Publication (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Bricklayer and his Union, Publication (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: The Bricklayers' Story, 1955; Publication (Box 116, Folder 6)
    Author: Harry C. Bates
    Notes: Reprint from the May, 1955, Issue of The American Federationist. 2 copies
- United States. Bureau of Apprenticeship and Training, Publication (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Bricklayers & Trowel Trades International Pension Fund, Publication (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Prescription drug plan of the Bricklayers Insurance and Welfare Fund, 1966-1967 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    Notes: Information flyers and posted memos - "
- United States. Bureau of Apprenticeship and Training., Publication (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the Mason Builders' Association of greater New York and certain Bricklayers Unions of the, 1936; Publication (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: How many bricks a day?, Publication (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Office of the U.S. Special Representative in Europe Paris, France -- O'Toole in Brussels MSA labor post; AFL Executive formerly with productivity council, 1950; Publication (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: National bricklayers' apprenticeship program and standards, 1947; Publication (Box 116, Folder 8)
    Author: United States. Bureau of Apprenticeship and Training
  - Item 5: National standards of apprenticeship for Terrazzo Workers, 1947; Publication (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: National standards of apprenticeship for tile setters, 1947; Publication (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: The Bricklayer and his Union, Publication (Box 116, Folder 8)
- United States. Bureau of Apprenticeship and Training, Publication (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Insurance and Welfare Fund, 1953-1955 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Pension Fund, 1953-1955 (Box 116, Folder 9)
- United States. Bureau of Apprenticeship and Training, Publication (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Report on audit, Bricklayers, Masons and Plasterers', 1925; Publication (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Semi-Annual report of the Bricklayers and Masons, 1891; Publication (Box 116, Folder 10)
- NABET (National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians), Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, 1955; Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1955 (Apr.-May,Aug.- Dec.)
  - Item 2: Bulletin, 1956; Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.1:no.1-3,5-6 (1956)
  - Item 3: Bulletin, 1957; Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.2:no.1-3,5-8 (1957)
- NABET (National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians), Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Misc correspondence regarding Union dues and cards, 1955-1958 (Box 117, Folder 2)
- NABET (National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians), Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, 1954; Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Financial Report for fiscal year 1959-1960 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: General Tire & Rubber Company - Letter to "Members of the Metropolitan NY Local #11", 1956; Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    Notes: Regarding purchase of car tires at a discount
- NABET (National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians), Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Financial report for 1960-1961 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Financial report for 1961-1962 (Box 117, Folder 4)
- Brooklyn Central Labor Union, Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Seventeenth Season of Brooklyn Central Labor Union Annual festival, 1900; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: Very brittle. Program
  - Item 2: Tenth Season of Brooklyn Central Labor Union Annual festival, 1893; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
- Brooklyn Labor Lyceum Association, Publication (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: By-laws of the Brooklyn Labor Lyceum Association, 1896; Publication (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: To organized labor of Brooklyn, New York & Vicinity, 1893; Publication (Box 117, Folder 6)
    Notes: Very brittle. Letter
- International Broom & Whisk Makers' Union, Publication (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Monthly Letter from International Broom & Whisk Makers' Union, 1952; Publication (Box 117, Folder 7)
    Notes: Jan.-Apr., June (1952)
- BSEIU (Building Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance, 1963; Publication (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Pension Plan, 1955; Publication (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Pensions, 1955; Publication (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Pensions/welfare - annual report 1960, Publication (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Winning new benefits for members through welfare plans, 1954; Publication (Box 118, Folder 1)
    Author: Dept. of Research and Education Building Service Empl. International Union.
  - Item 6: Your Group Insurance Plan, 1953; Publication (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Building Service Employees' Pension Fund of Upstate New York, 1968; Publication (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Employees Retirement Plan - Trust Agreement and Pension Plan for Local Union Employees, 1955; Publication (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Group Insurance Plan for Local No. 200, 1968; Publication (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: The Pension plan of the Carpenters Pension Trust Fund for Northern California, 1958; Publication (Box 118, Folder 1)
- BSEIU (Building Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Detroit hospital's workers go on strike for union recognition, 1948-1949 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Elevator help seek pay rise in Phila., 1948-1949 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Gravediggers may break with union, 1948-1949 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: High court upholds state ban on forced union membership, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Hotel workers get rise, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Legion Honors AFL aide, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: negotiations started, 1948-1949 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Nurses seek rise in pay, 1948-1949 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: O'Dwyer praises unions, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Pay award is won by building staffs, 1949-1950 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Peace seen nearer in apartment row, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Realty union ousts 2 labor experts, 1949-1950 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Sign building service pact, 1948-1949 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Strike emergency services, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Students continue work in cemetery, 1949; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: U-M Janitors threaten strike, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Wage averts apartment strike, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Wives ask arbiter for burial strike, 1949; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: Workers get $2/wk rise in Bronx Dev., 1948-1949 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: 3,000 delay strike in schools of city, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: 4 years at college given by Service Union to 2 sons and 2 daughters of members, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: 41 pickets and lawyer paroled, 1948-1949 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 23: Cemetery parley due to be renewed, 1948-1949 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 24: Cemetery strike still deadlocked, 1949; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 25: Few garment area elevators to run Tuesday, 1949; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 26: Landlords reject demands of union, 1949-1950 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 27: Polo grounds gate keepers win pay rise equal to wage at other baseball parks, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 28: Union pickets union, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 29: Union sets up scholarships, 1949-1950 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 30: 16 union scholarships, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 31: 275 Gravediggers get gifts from Cardinal, 1949-1950 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 32: 500 Service employees end loft building strike., 1948-1949 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 33: Building service back to normal, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 34: Building Service row in hands of Mediator, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 35: Building workers ask new pay rises, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 36: Building workers get 6-7/8 cents pay rise, 1948-1949 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 37: Burial strikers vote to quite CIO, all take anti-Communist oath, 1949; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 38: Cardinal directs 100 digging graves, 1949; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 39: Cardinal directs as his Seminarians dig ninety graves, 1949; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 40: Cardinal starts doubled crew digging graves, 1949-1950 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 41: City radio use asked by Sanitation Union, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 42: Cleaner's strike near, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
- BSEIU (Building Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Apartment strike is set for April 20, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Apartment strike off until Monday, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Board sets hearings on building pay issue, 1949-1950 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Building strike called 'definite', 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Building walkout seems inevitable, 1949-1950 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Building workers bar owners' plan, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Elevators in use - Return to jobs speeded -normal service this morning, 1949-1950 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Loft owners win overtime test suit, 1949-1950 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Moves to avert building strike, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Service staff pay in city analyzed, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Session set today in building dispute, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Apartment strike is ended, issues go to fact finders, phone picketing due today, 1949-1950 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Diggers settle cemetery strike - Cardinal reports 8-1/3% pay rise, 1949-1950 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Rise in pay sought by building staffs, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: Strike emergency services, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 3)
- BSEIU (Building Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: 47 Sanitation men, 'loitering on job' suspended by city, 1950-1951 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: 5 more suspended in garbage tie-up, 1950-1951 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: 95 Sanitation men order to trial for 2 slowdowns, 1950-1951 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Apartment strike nearer an accord after 2-hour talk, 1950-1951 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Arbitration offer in elevator tie-up weighed by union, 1950-1951 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: City apartments and offices face elevator strike, 1950-1951 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Garbage collections described as normal, 1950-1951 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Hardships start for many in City, 1950-1951 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Hospital strike voted, 1950-1951 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: NLRB rejects bids by two unions at Field's, 1950-1951 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Quick trials asked in refuse slow-up, 1950-1951 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Rival union assails sanitation 'strike', 1950-1951 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Sanitation crews restored to jobs, 1950-1951 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Sanitation head suspends 17 more, 1950-1951 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Sanitation union asks new parley, 1950-1951 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Six hospitals refuse returning strikers, 1950-1951 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Supplies shut off in hospitals strike, 1950-1951 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Vandalism charged on garbage trucks, 1950-1951 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Apartment strike due this morning in 1,000 buildings, 1950-1951 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Service strike set in 2,000 buildings, 1950-1951 (Box 118, Folder 4)
- BSEIU (Building Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Sanitation men call off slowdown as city acts to suspend laggards, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Sanitation union attacks inaction on pay..., 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Sanitation union begins slowdown, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Strikers jostle hospital staffs, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Volunteers work in hospital strike, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Walkout expected to spread before state-led parleys are resumed Monday, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Wave of 'sickness' hits garbage men, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: 3-year pact signed by service union, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Building service walkout in Bronx Sunday night looms, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Minnesota women take over hospital strikers' work, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Peace hopes rise in Bronx walkout, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Police cars guard sanitation trucks, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Sanitation pay row aired, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: 16 Buildings yield quickly in strike, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: 3 year peace pact halts lift strike in city apartments, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: 360,000 garbage cans untouched as sanitation slowdown spreads, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: 4 children saved, fire kills mother, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 18: 5 day week proposed by sanitation union, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 19: Apartment house strike, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 20: Armed gang halts sanitation truck, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 21: Baltimore strike eased by janitors, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 22: Bronx talks end service walkout, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 23: Building service men out in Bronx, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 24: Building workers win pay increase, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 25: Bureau of labor problems urged city doubles holiday garbage...., 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 26: Cardinal to help bury dead today as Seminarians replace strikers, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 27: City set to replace garbage men if union orders slowdown today, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 28: City weighing plan to cut labor rows, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 29: Custodians threaten walkout in schools, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 30: Drop wieboldt dividend plan for employees, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 31: Elevator strike in offices today, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 32: Elevator strike may be averted, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 33: Elevator strikes hit 4 apartments, 1951; Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)